foreign
[Music]
they take longer time to Consolidated
the consolidate the accounts and then
report Fair results
cavity
ten percent foreign
so as of now based on 2023 March results
there is not even one company which is
worth freshly investing into
teacher
so before we move ahead my name is
please make sure to get your Holdings in
order and I mean portfolio already
so that once these new companies
investment what the company investors
so make sure to get out of some weak
stocks make sure to send Holdings to
Holdings
with the quantities
they'll be able to send it across so
that you are ready to take the most
Advantage so Prasad with that being said
I think such a huge giant and also
impending merger with HDFC until there
is big news in the pipeline or big news
gather big updates in terms of
operations in the pipeline but is it a
right time to enter into HDFC Bank
results
so don't buy into that company but if
you have a stock in your portfolio
continue the ride only if it crosses
2245 or so accordingly
foreign
General prospects whether consensus
among the fund managers
to 11.66
but if you can wait wait for some Norton
because there will be more companies
coming out with better results and then
there will be more scope for them to
grow further also but foreign
results on foreign
[Music]
foreign
and thank you everyone for watching